Vishal Sudhakar Zambare (1) Featured



Associate Consultant/Senior Analyst seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, Automation Design and Dev., Agile Methodology, Technical Analysis, System Analysis, Solution Design, Shell Scripting, Python, Java



Current Location: Navi Mumbai Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Navi Mumbai, Pune Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: MS/M.Sc(Science) [Computer Science]

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Associate Consultant/Senior Analyst, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, Agile Methodology, Technical Analysis, System Analysis, Solution Design, Shell

Scripting, Python, Java, Automation Framework

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

I am a versatile software engineer with 4+ years of proven industry experience who likes to challenge himself with new challenges. I like to grow every time I have a new task at hand and the versatility of my profile reflects my philosophy towards work. My experience in multiple technology stacks is my strongest trait which depicts my habit and desire to learn new technologies. Apart from picking up skills, I also like to train people on my strengths and have a proven experience of delivering successful university level workshops

Work Experience

Capgemini as ASSOCIATE CONSULTANT/SENIOR ANALYST - IT Mar 2019 to Nov 2020

- Duration: March 2019 to November 2020
- Senior Software Developer / Technical Lead Automation Framework Design, Development, Sprint management, code review, POCs, technical guidance, etc.
- Gained prowess in IPC mechanisms, API integration, Solution Design, Git workflows, Agile methodologies and implementing Agile.
- Made most out of the opportunity to work in a multi-programming environment Java, Python, C#, C++, Batch Scripting, Shell Scripting.
- Designed a test prediction system for pre-execution analysis of the probability of test case success/failure.

COLLABERA TECHNOLOGIES PVT. LTD. as Software Engineer

Apr 2018 to Mar 2019

- Duration: April 2018 to March 2019
- Third party payroll for Capgemini India

PANKANIS TECHNOLOGIES PVT. LTD. as Associate Developer

May 2017 to Mar 2018

Java Developer - Oracle MAF, Oracle ADF - Java Beans (Live product experience). Android Developer - API integration and UI designing for a couple of applications. Duration: May 2017 to March 2017

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computer Science) from Mumbai University in 2017

PG: MS/M.Sc(Science) (Computer Science) from University Of Mumbai, Mumbai in 2019

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Python			
CORE JAVA			
Shell, Python			
JavaScript			
Oracle AD, MAF			
SOCKETS			
Linux, Windows			
Emacs, Eclipse, NetBeans			
Android Studio			
Qt Creator, PyCharm			
Intellij IDEA. Jira, Ranorex			
Bitbucket, Gitlab			
Confluence, SharePoint			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent

Category: General Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization